http://www.soap-making-essentials.com/privacy-policy.html

Soap Making Essentials
Get Hooked on Soap Making!
Menu
Home
WelcomeMy StoryAbout SoapWhat's New!Soap Gallery
MaterialsSuppliesSoap Making OilsEssential OilsSoap Making AdditivesSodium Hydroxide
MethodsHow to Make SoapRebatching SoapHot Process Rebatch
FormulasSoap RecipesPalm Free Soap RecipesBasic Soap RecipesBath & Body RecipesCleaning Recipes
IdeasDecorative IdeasPackaging IdeasSoap Selling Ideas
ReferenceLye CalculatorsSoap Making SuppliersSoap Making ForumsSoap Making TermsSoap Making QuestionsTroubleshooting GuideFrequently Asked QuestionsContact Info
by
FreeFind
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWe recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Soap Making Essentials, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Soap Making Essentials strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.Personal InformationSoap Making Essentials collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.This information is collected if you request information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsWe may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Soap Making Essentials to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.DoubleClick DART CookieThe DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. When you visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on your browser. The data gathered (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, visit the following links.Double ClickGoogle Privacy CenterChildren's On-line Privacy Protection ActThis website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's On-line Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.Non-Personal InformationIn some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.Release of InformationIf Soap Making Essentials is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honours any opt-out requests you might make of us.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.Updates and Effective DateSoap Making Essentials reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to Soap Making Essentials Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Some of the links on this site are affiliate links. If you buy a product through them, I receive a small commission which helps me provide the free information you find on this site. Thank you for your support!
Like This Page?
Facebook Comments
Site Sponsors
If you've found this site to be helpful in expanding your soap making knowledge and would like to make a SMALL donation to help with the cost of maintaining this site, your support would be greatly appreciated.
Recent Articles
Forgot to add the lye!Well, it was getting quite late last night and I was finishing up my last batch of soap.
I got my water mixture out of the fridge and whisked it into Read More
Allergic to nuts/coconutsI'm interested in making my own soap and shampoo bars, but my young son is allergic to all nuts and possibly to coconut. Is there a recipe I can use or Read More
Home  |  What's New!  |  Contact Info  |  Privacy Policy
BY CATHY WINSBY, © 2008 - 2016, SOAP-MAKING-ESSENTIALS.COM, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
All content on this website is for informational purposes only.
